♪ Darkness and light mingle ♪
♪ Dreams fade in reality ♪
♪ The path ahead is long and twisted ♪
♪ Ready to confront destiny ♪
♪ Sail against the tide fearlessly ♪
♪ Fight against the fate determinedly ♪
♪ Fly high ♪
♪ Traverse the land of dream ♪
♪ Bright & sky, reflected in my eyes ♪
♪ Born to shine, born to fight ♪
♪ My heart never changes ♪
♪ My dreams are not bound by time ♪
♪ Wandering in endless darkness ♪
♪ Embrace a new life ♪
♪ The roaring fire shakes the sky ♪
♪ Wait to wake up ♪
♪ Oh my life ♪
♪ I'm here to change the world ♪
= Full-time Magister =
I'm Mo Fan, and I'm a ninth grader.
= Senior High School Entrance Examination =
This examination
has almost driven me mad.
Not because I'm a bad student,
but because the exam was on MAGIC!
Time to go home!
It's finally over!
Come on let's go.
Ever since I fell asleep
with this pendant on three months ago,
everything has changed.
All everybody talks about now is magic.
Hey, isn't that Mo Fan?
He turned in his exam so early.
He must not have understood the subject matter!
I thought it was quite difficult.
I couldn't fill in
all seven uses of Level 1 Light Magic,
the last question on the exam.
Hey Mu Bai,
you're smart,
you must have gotten all of them!
It's just an entrance exam on basic theory
for Magic Senior High School.
The key is what talent we'll receive
during the Magic Awakening.
Of course,
those who don't pass the exam will never be Mages.
Mu Bai, you'll be fine,
your entire family has the Ice talent,
you'll definitely be Ice-talented, too!
Ice is powerful.
I hope I get it, too.
Fire is better.
But it's really rare.
I heard Fire is still not the most powerful.
= Shuilan Junior High =
Dad, what are you doing here?
To pick you up.
How did your exam go?
What a mess!
I studied for three whole months,
but the exam covered nine years of material!
How was I supposed to pass it?
Don't worry,
I found you a job as a driver to the neighboring city.
Uncle Guangfeng will teach you,
and the salary is good.
4,000 to 5,000 a month!
It's not bad
to start working when you're young.
Dad, I want to study!
I mean, I want to be a Mage!
I know being a Mage is a good path.
You have plans,
and you don't want to be a driver like me.
But you know that your exam results
aren't high enough to meet the entrance requirement.
I'm serious!
I don't want to be a miserable loser
either in the old world or in the Magic world.
Well,
if you're serious about it, I'll think of something.
Dad, thank you!
I'll become a great Mage
who is respected by everyone!
Good.
Let's go home!
= Shuilan Junior High =
Right bro,
Mu Ningxue has come back from the Capital!
I saw her this morning,
she's even prettier than before!
Oh.
Yo, what, no response?
How should I respond?
Mo Fan, wait for me!
Come on, are you not excited at all?
Mr. Mu,
please do me a favor.
Please!
I know you can get them to admit my son
if you talk to them.
Mo Jiaxing,
it's one thing for your son to fail an exam,
but he once tried to elope with the heiress of Mu Family!
So tell me,
why should I help you after what happened?
It was indeed Mo Fan's fault,
he shouldn't have done that.
Fortunately we found them pretty soon,
and no one was hurt.
He didn't do anything to Miss Mu.
I've faithfully served the Mu Family all these years,
please help me one last time!
My son is serious about becoming a Mage!
It's too late for that,
a failure is a failure!
You should have educated him better
if you wanted him to pass.
Without my help last time,
you'd have already been kicked out!
Your son might be too young and dumb to understand it,
but you're an adult who's worked for a long time,
don't you understand that
Miss Mu is way out of your league?
He really wants to be a Mage!
Mr. Mu,
I'm willing to do anything
if... if you help me!
Oh? You really mean it?
Master Mu has always wanted you to move away.
Getting admitted to Magic School is expensive,
but it costs more than money.
Well, I'll consider it if you
pledge your house to me.
Pledge my house to you?
Your house is a dump,
but the land isn't.
Deal.
What's wrong?
What is wrong with the world?
How is it so cruel?
The poor and weak are always bullied!
Son, I have good news!
I got you admitted to Magic School!
Eat.
You did?
One of my classmates
happens to be the director there,
he promised me to get you in!
Promise me you'll study harder.
Son, I believe in you!
Okay.
Oh, one more thing.
I plan to rent the house out
while you're in school.
I'm always driving for work,
Xinxia lives at school,
the house will be empty
if you live at school, too.
Okay.
So, I heard that Miss Mu is back?
Dad, all I can think of now is to study Magic,
to earn a lot of money for you and Xinxia,
and to buy houses for you all to live in!
Your son is going to be the greatest Mage ever!
Good! Good!
= Mu Ningxue =
You...
Mo Fan, let's go.
But... To where?
Wherever, as long as it's not here!
Alright then.
Mo Jiaxing!
Your son's got some stones!
He tried to elope with Ningxue!
Does he have a death wish?
I'm sorry, I'm sorry,
it's all my fault!
Please just punish me.
Forgive Mo Fan!
He's just a dumb child.
A child?
Pretty clever for a child!
He tried to seduce and kidnap my daughter!
Mo Fan, this is your last warning.
I'll break your legs one by one
if you see her again!
= Welcome =
Students,
today is your first day at Sky Magic High School.
Welcome to the haven of magic!
I didn't realize we have our Magic Awakening today.
I'm nervous!
Me, too!
I want to become a Wind Mage.
I hope Wind will become my talent.
Wind is useless!
Fire is where it's at.
But only a few people can awaken it.  -Cheer up, man!
Only two or three in each class.  -You'll receive a powerful talent! Yes!
= Sky Magic High School =
This badge is very important.
= Class 8 Grade 1 =
Students,
when your talent is awoken,
the badge will change to its corresponding color.
Cyan corresponds to Wind,
red corresponds to Fire,
gold corresponds to Light.
What?
No. 48, Mo Fan,
the last one.
You're lucky to be here.
Called in a favor, eh?
You jerk, leave him alone!
We all know that he could never pass the exam!
He'll embarrass himself
if he can't awaken a talent.
Man, ignore him.
You can awaken a powerful talent!
Powerful?
He'll be lucky if he can awaken that weak Light talent.
He can't compare with Mu Bai!
Mu Bai, put your right hand on the Crystal Ball,
and focus.
Yes sir.
You're from the Mu Family?
I hope you'll awaken Ice.
Let's begin!
Amazing!
Ice talent!
Yeah!
Mu Bai has awoken the Ice talent!
The stars on the badge
will show the strength of your talent.
Usually there are 7 dark stars after Awakening.
But Mu Bai has one bright star,
meaning that his talent is more powerful.
He's handsome and talented!
He's smart!
Wow.
Nice, I want the Ice talent, too!
Why is this loser here again?
No worries,
I'll show him how useless he is.
Alright, next, No. 2!
= Wind =
= Earth =
= Water =
= Light =
None of the others had a bright star.
It's my turn.
No. 48, Mo Fan.
That's Mo Fan?
I heard he had to pull a favor to get in.
That's right!
Don't be sad
if you awoke a Light or Water talent!
At least you are better than him!
Alright, put your right hand on it.
Relax,
keep your hand stable,
or it won't work.
So he's the transfer student.
I hope he awakens something,
otherwise everybody will laugh at me!
Come on!
I'll even take a Light talent!
Anything is better than failing!
What?
It's purple?
Cyan for Wind,
blue for Water,
brown for Earth,
gold for Light,
red for Fire,
but what does purple correspond to?!
Thunder!
The Thunder talent!
Someone has awoken Thunder!
What?! Thunder?! For real?
Let's go see.
No way!
Barely 1 in 1,000 people can awaken Thunder!
It's really the Thunder talent!
He's the only one among all the students!
Amazing!
Fire talent?
It can't compete with Thunder at all!
A Thunder talent?
His teacher must be thrilled!
After all, Thunder is the most powerful element.
Make way, make way.
Don't push.  -Let me have a look.
It's really the Thunder talent!
Please excuse me.
Let me have a closer look.
♪ Standing at the edge of the world ♪
♪ Gazing upon the brightest star in the sky ♪
♪ Stay true to my faith ♪
♪ The fire in my soul will never extinguish ♪
♪ Never surrender ♪
♪ The flowers that never wither ♪
♪ Something is growing ♪
♪ Guided by the light in the far end ♪
♪ We sail forward ♪
♪ The dancing flowers ♪
♪ They don't want to wither ♪
♪ The wind is howling ♪
♪ Let it blow ♪
♪ Standing at the edge of the world ♪
♪ Gazing upon the brightest star in the sky ♪
♪ Whatever storms await me ♪
♪ They can't blow out the fire in my soul ♪
♪ What the future holds ♪
♪ Is still yet to be discovered ♪
♪ What lurks in the darkness scares me not ♪
♪ Let the fire swallows the wilderness ♪
♪ Let the world see a better future ♪